On the surface, creating a list of items is simple enough.
Android includes a Scroll View into which you can place any
linear layout that in turn arranges each item it contains into a vertical list.
Note the items which have fallen off the bottom off the linear layout. And
therefore aren't currently visible in that UI. The Scroll View,
as the name suggests, will let the user scroll through the contents of
the layout it contains. But there's a challenge associated with that approach on
a device with limited memory, and where touch responsiveness is
critically important. If you have 50 items in a list and
can fit 10 items on screen at any given time. What's the minimum number of
views you'd need to create in order to scroll through every item on the list?
The answer might not be immediately obvious but think about ways in which you
can be more efficient in your use of the views used to display the entire list.